<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1659465823">
		<path>Pac-Man (USA) (Namco).zip</path>
		<hash>15D202D8</hash>
		<region>248</region>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<genreid>258</genreid>
		<genre>Action / Labyrinth,Action</genre>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<releasedate>19931101T230000</releasedate>
		<video>media/videos/Pac-man (namco) 350395771afe4cdbde1a8f61b8a58568.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>media/thumbnails/Pac-man (namco) 9ef8aaec739e7851b4ac6a885cea68ef.png</thumbnail>
		<image>media/images/Pac-man (namco) 8126255bbac977e45314e711ea363b89.png</image>
		<desc>One of the most popular and influential games of the 1980's, Pac-Man stars a little, yellow dot-muncher who works his way around to clear a maze of the various dots and fruit which inhabit the board.

Pac-Man's goal is continually challenged by four ghosts: The shy blue ghost Bashful (Inky), the trailing red ghost Shadow (Blinky), the fast pink ghost Speedy (Pinky), and the forgetful orange ghost Pokey (Clyde).  One touch from any of these ghosts means a loss of life for Pac-Man.

Pac-Man can turn the tables on his pursuers by eating of the four Energizers located within the maze.  During this time, the ghosts turn blue, and Pac-Man can eat them for bonus points.  This only lasts for a limited amount of time, as the ghost's eyes float back to their center box, and regenerate to chase after Pac-Man again.

Survive a few rounds of gameplay, and be treated to humorous intermissions between Pac-Man and the ghosts.</desc>
		<rating>0.80000</rating>
		<name>Pac-Man (Namco)</name>
	</game>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1659465693">
		<path>Donkey Kong Classics (USA, Europe).zip</path>
		<hash>17EC0CC7</hash>
		<lastplayed>19800101T010451</lastplayed>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<region>248</region>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<genreid>3840</genreid>
		<genre>Compilation</genre>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<releasedate>19880930T230000</releasedate>
		<video>media/videos/Donkey Kong Classics cfc900e642ac2b8a26bd8284478cbc98.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>media/thumbnails/Donkey Kong Classics c103f4a487ae4f541abc25a79b3359e5.png</thumbnail>
		<image>media/images/Donkey Kong Classics d62c48e366bd26fc0b847865d2634d34.png</image>
		<desc>Donkey Kong Classics features both the original Donkey Kong and Donkey Kong Jr. on a single cartridge. In Donkey Kong, you need to guide Mario safely up the scaffolding to rescue his girlfriend, Pauline. In Donkey Kong Jr., the roles are reversed; you control Jr. who needs to rescue his father, who has been captured by Mario.</desc>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<rating>0.70000</rating>
		<name>Donkey Kong Classics</name>
	</game>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1659485937">
		<path>Super Mario Bros. (Japan, USA).zip</path>
		<hash>3337EC46</hash>
		<lastplayed>20220802T231722</lastplayed>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<region>11</region>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<genreid>257</genreid>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<releasedate>19850912T230000</releasedate>
		<video>media/videos/Super Mario Bros. a374f136bd8dd6315693b879772bc4ce.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>media/thumbnails/Super Mario Bros. 6534f6de836049e91b1d84ee222042be.png</thumbnail>
		<image>media/images/Super Mario Bros. c0eefb08fbda01f216029dcd6ea99fe6.png</image>
		<desc>The Princess has been kidnapped by the evil Bowser, and it is up to Mario and brother Luigi to save the day.

The first ever platform adventure for the Mario Brothers has the player exploring level after level, with Bowser to contend with as the end of level boss. Power-ups include the Super Mushroom, which increases Mario's size and power, the fire flower, allowing him to shoot fireballs at enemies, and the ever important starman for a short burst of invincibility.

Each level includes a bonus section filled with coins plus a shortcut through the level, plenty of bad buys and obstacles to get past, and an end of level flag, in which the higher the player grabs it, the more points are awarded to them. Certain levels also include warp points, which takes the player to higher levels.</desc>
		<rating>0.80000</rating>
		<name>Super Mario Bros.</name>
	</game>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1659465437">
		<path>Super Mario Bros. 3 (USA).zip</path>
		<hash>85A79D9C</hash>
		<lastplayed>20220802T231756</lastplayed>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<region>248</region>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<genreid>257</genreid>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<releasedate>19900211T230000</releasedate>
		<video>media/videos/Super Mario Bros. 3 b352dba89115779a600ffcfb85ecaac7.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>media/thumbnails/Super Mario Bros. 3 d54788ffed6d84a92568c31bfaf1f69a.png</thumbnail>
		<image>media/images/Super Mario Bros. 3 fa2a3df5ef2ac49c5d72157719d113c9.png</image>
		<desc>Bowser is back, and along with the Bowser kids, he's out to spoil Mario's day once again. 

This time, along with nabbing the Princess, the Bowser crew have also taken the magic wands from the Kings of each land and turned them into creatures.
It's up to Mario and Luigi to get back the magic wands, defeat Bowser, and save the Princess all before the day is done.

Old and new power-ups abound in each level for the Mario Brothers, including the return of the Super Mushroom and Fire Flower, plus the new power-ups including the frog suit, the warp flute, and the most important of all, the leaf, which allows the player to fly and attack enemies with your tail.</desc>
		<rating>0.85000</rating>
		<name>Super Mario Bros. 3</name>
	</game>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1659465808">
		<path>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles (U) [h1].zip</path>
		<hash>DF45210E</hash>
		<region>248</region>
		<genreid>257</genreid>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<releasedate>19890601T230000</releasedate>
		<video>media/videos/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles dd08cc90d5e0ed3b3c46a936f7ebd41d.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>media/thumbnails/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles d7b9f3caa067ff3d12856565aa25e059.png</thumbnail>
		<image>media/images/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles 6302a6aff8649649662925aa2569c8b9.png</image>
		<desc>With April O'Neil held hostage by The Shredder's thugs, Bebop and Rocksteady, once again, it's up to the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles to come to her rescue!  Play as all four of the turtle heroes, rescue April, and then rescue your sensei Splinter from Mecha-Turtles clutches than go after The Shredder deep in the bowels of The Technodrome itself.

Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles is an action game based on the late eighties/early nineties cartoon series of the same name. Play as Leonardo, Michaelangelo, Donatello and Raphael (one turtle only, but the ability to swap between turtles at any time) as you save your friends and battle The Shredder and his cronies. There are no 'lives', as such - when you lose a turtle, he becomes 'captured', and you cannot use him again until you rescue him from a place hidden in the overworld.

Gameplay takes place in two perspectives: a top-down view, which lets you run around and explore buildings, sewers and other places. When entering places from the top-down view, the perspective shifts to a side-scrolling view, where most of the battling takes place. In addition to each turtle's main weapon, sub-weapons (such as shuriken) can be acquired, to use at foes - these have a limited use.</desc>
		<rating>0.64999</rating>
		<name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles</name>
	</game>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1659465836">
		<path>Ice Climber (USA, Europe).zip</path>
		<hash>70044A74</hash>
		<lastplayed>20220802T010000</lastplayed>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<region>248</region>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<genreid>257</genreid>
		<genre>Platform,Action</genre>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<releasedate>19850930T230000</releasedate>
		<video>media/videos/Ice Climber 421075cec83d0d3d3d8c7cf11cfe40a9.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>media/thumbnails/Ice Climber adeafb5174bea23e05c2b3f2795235ef.png</thumbnail>
		<image>media/images/Ice Climber 86b9132920dea16ef6f1377be66427da.png</image>
		<desc>In Ice Climber one or two players need to climb their way to the top of 32 different mountains. Each mountain is broken up into eight levels of platforms along with a bonus stage at the top. Attempting to stop you from making upward progress are different creatures ranging from polar bears to condors as well as treacherous landscapes with falling icicles, moving platforms, and icy floors. To help out, your only weapon is a mallet which can be used to knock out enemies as well as bust away bricks in the platforms to give you some room to jump up to the next level. When you finally reach the top, it's time to move on to the next, more difficult level.</desc>
		<rating>0.60000</rating>
		<name>Ice Climber</name>
	</game>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1659465635">
		<path>Dragon Warrior (USA).zip</path>
		<hash>CAAF5C6B</hash>
		<region>248</region>
		<genreid>768</genreid>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<developer>Enix</developer>
		<releasedate>19890731T230000</releasedate>
		<video>media/videos/Dragon Warrior 756adc83704c90765d4f1958210927d7.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>media/thumbnails/Dragon Warrior 582bd074fbf0176a0bf3bacebf97aa1c.png</thumbnail>
		<image>media/images/Dragon Warrior 16d22bfed51258c749d5332e3a5d10ee.png</image>
		<desc>Dragon Warrior is the first famous console RPG. You assume the role of a descendant of Erdrick, a brave warrior of the past. Once upon a time, Erdrick defeated the evil Dragonlord with the help of the Ball of Light. Now, Dragonlord stole the Ball of Light, and your mission is to recover it and to restore peace in the world.

In Dragon Warrior, you move your character around in a top-down world. In cities and palaces you can talk to people, rest in inns and buy stuff in shops. There's a variety of weapons, equipment and armor to buy. 

When wandering around in the wilderness, you occasionally encounter enemies, and fight them from 1st person perspective. Combat is turn based: you select menu options while fighting - you can attack with your weapon, cast a spell (using up some of your magic energy), use and item or try to run. Killing monsters gives you experience, and, as is typical for RPGs, you level up and improve your stats when you gain enough experience. 

Like in later RPGs, you have limited hit points, lose them when you are attacked by enemies, and die when you run out of them. When your character dies in a battle, he is automatically restored in a nearby town.</desc>
		<rating>0.70000</rating>
		<name>Dragon Warrior</name>
	</game>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1659465500">
		<path>Q-bert (U).zip</path>
		<hash>19AD4071</hash>
		<lastplayed>20220802T005850</lastplayed>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<region>248</region>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<genreid>2816</genreid>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game,Action</genre>
		<publisher>Ultra Games</publisher>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<releasedate>19890201T230000</releasedate>
		<video>media/videos/Qbert c0b2bef382bb2f5e2234f9c8fa19730f.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>media/thumbnails/Qbert 624718fde7acee55fc5ad5044d651e99.png</thumbnail>
		<image>media/images/Qbert 61bc345d2157c677fc41738923dc61cb.png</image>
		<desc>Q*bert is a conversion of the popular arcade game. The goal is to change all of the tiles on a pyramid to the target color. To do this you guide Q*bert around the pyramid, and every tile he hops on will change color. On early levels, a single hop will change the tile to the desired color, but on later levels you may need to hop on a tile multiple times or even avoid hopping on a tile multiple times! Trying to stop Q*bert are many different creatures which wander around the board, including Coily the snake, Slick and Sam, and falling balls. On the edge of the board are floating discs; if Q*bert jumps on one of these discs when the snake is in pursuit, the snake will fall off  the board while Q*bert is safely transported to the top.</desc>
		<rating>0.80000</rating>
		<name>Q*bert</name>
	</game>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1659465866">
		<path>Super Mario World.zip</path>
		<hash>82392F0D</hash>
		<region>11</region>
		<genreid>257</genreid>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<publisher>J.Y. Company</publisher>
		<developer>Hummer Team</developer>
		<releasedate>19941231T230000</releasedate>
		<video>media/videos/Super Mario World 54ca2004a518a4c8d8c3662ff0bd4311.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>media/thumbnails/Super Mario World 672924cf9428b9a4046e2ac80e4dcb20.png</thumbnail>
		<image>media/images/Super Mario World 13613d88a9c20d06d1630d3dde5184b2.png</image>
		<desc>Super Mario World is a bootleg port of the SNES launch title of the same name, developed by Hummer Team and released in 1995. This is one of the more well-known examples of pirate ports to the NES, as it comparatively manages to retain most of the elements that defined the SNES original without sacrificing too much quality.</desc>
		<rating>0.55000</rating>
		<name>Super Mario World</name>
	</game>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1659465596">
		<path>Excitebike (Japan, USA).zip</path>
		<hash>2BB33C69</hash>
		<region>248</region>
		<genreid>1537</genreid>
		<genre>Race, Driving,Sports</genre>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<releasedate>19851017T230000</releasedate>
		<video>media/videos/Excitebike b28df5031cf9d6b2a9ca24be0ae23e59.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>media/thumbnails/Excitebike 422ed50d8f182078631f895bc2de87b2.png</thumbnail>
		<image>media/images/Excitebike ba90e1a7c672550f1fdd8c6689c839b7.png</image>
		<desc>Race by yourself against the clock or compete with other motocross riders on 5 tracks full of long straights, large jumps and obstacles to win the Excitebike championship.

Create your own tracks by placing jumps and obstacles of all different sizes and shapes on the track and choosing how many laps each race will have, then race against the clock or other riders to see how your track fares in competition.</desc>
		<rating>0.70000</rating>
		<name>Excitebike</name>
	</game>
</gameList>
