<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<folder source="Recalbox" timestamp="0">
		<path>Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (USA)</path>
		<name>Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (USA)</name>
	</folder>
	<folder source="Recalbox" timestamp="0">
		<path>Mario Kart 64 (USA)</path>
		<name>Mario Kart 64 (USA)</name>
	</folder>
	<folder source="Recalbox" timestamp="0">
		<path>Mario Party (USA)</path>
		<name>Mario Party (USA)</name>
	</folder>
	<folder source="Recalbox" timestamp="0">
		<path>Mario Party 2 (USA)</path>
		<name>Mario Party 2 (USA)</name>
	</folder>
	<folder source="Recalbox" timestamp="0">
		<path>Mario Party 3 (USA)</path>
		<name>Mario Party 3 (USA)</name>
	</folder>
	<folder source="Recalbox" timestamp="0">
		<path>Paper Mario (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es) (1)</path>
		<name>Paper Mario (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es) (1)</name>
	</folder>
	<folder source="Recalbox" timestamp="0">
		<path>Super Mario 64 (USA)</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64 (USA)</name>
	</folder>
	<folder source="Recalbox" timestamp="0">
		<path>Super Smash Bros. (USA)</path>
		<name>Super Smash Bros</name>
	</folder>
	<folder source="Recalbox" timestamp="0">
		<path>Superman (U) (M3) [!]</path>
		<name>Superman (U) (M3) [!]</name>
	</folder>
	<folder source="Recalbox" timestamp="0">
		<path>Star Wars - Rogue Squadron (USA)</path>
		<name>Star Wars - Rogue Squadron (USA)</name>
	</folder>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1672717459">
		<path>Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (USA)/Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (USA).n64</path>
		<hash>2E72659E</hash>
		<region>248</region>
		<genreid>768</genreid>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<releasedate>19981122T230000</releasedate>
		<video>media/videos/Legend Of Zelda - Ocarina Of Time The 33396aac9efda5dcd349e1b13dbadc7a.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>media/thumbnails/Legend Of Zelda - Ocarina Of Time The 5f8503adfe5ca917101bc18b83269b24.png</thumbnail>
		<image>media/images/Legend Of Zelda - Ocarina Of Time The 40d0d3650809c0ddcaf3d72a72be35db.png</image>
		<desc>Ganondorf, the evil King of Thieves, is on the move, threatening the peaceful land of Hyrule. He is determined to steal his way into the legendary Sacred Realm in hopes of harnessing the power of the mythical Triforce. As the young hero Link, it is your destiny to thwart Ganondorf's evil schemes. Navi, your guardian fairy, will guide you as you venture through the many regions of Hyrule, from the volcanic caves of Death Mountain to the treacherous waters of Zora's Domain. Before you complete this epic quest, you'll delve into deadly dungeons, collect weapons of great power and learn the spells you need to conquer the most irresistible force of all-time.</desc>
		<rating>0.95000</rating>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda : Ocarina of Time</name>
	</game>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1672717467">
		<path>Mario Kart 64 (USA)/Mario Kart 64 (USA).n64</path>
		<hash>2BCEE11C</hash>
		<region>248</region>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<genreid>1537</genreid>
		<genre>Sports,Race, Driving</genre>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<releasedate>19970209T230000</releasedate>
		<video>media/videos/Mario Kart 64 238f6f76b1913930482662430075bfc2.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>media/thumbnails/Mario Kart 64 f4d5321bdc58beb32ac2ff6e452d1b21.png</thumbnail>
		<image>media/images/Mario Kart 64 10323e6a5c131849e31af39e847c1dd1.png</image>
		<desc>Mario Kart 64 races eight familiar faces, including Mario, Bowser and Yoshi, on four progressively tougher four-track circuits. Wide curves and gentle banks mark the Mushroom Cup tracks. Your commute gets notably tougher on the Flower Cup, though. The player will have to dodge semis rumbling on Toad's Turnpike and bounding boulders on fogbound Choco Mountain! Star Cup tracks range from the icy surfaces of Sherbet Land to the lava lakes of Bowser's Castle. The true test of karting competence, though, comes on the four tracks in Special Cup. Zip through the dark caves and green hillsides of Donkey Kong's Jungle Parkway, cling to the sheer cliffs of Yoshi Valley and hustle over haunted Banshee Boardwalk before tackling the longest track in the game: neon-lit Rainbow Road. 

The game offers two camera angles and three engine sizes: 50cc, 100cc and 150cc. You can gain even more speed by mastering the power slide technique or grabbing Super Star power-ups. Each kart has distinctive handling, acceleration and top speed capabilities. Light karts like Princess's smoothly steer through tight corners, but run the constant risk of getting flattened by heavy karts, like Donkey Kong's. Shells that you fire at rival racers, Bananas that make them skid out and Lightning Bolts that make them small and very slow are just a few of the game's unique power-ups.</desc>
		<rating>0.80000</rating>
		<name>Mario Kart 64</name>
	</game>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1672717459">
		<path>Mario Party (USA)/Mario Party (USA).n64</path>
		<hash>CBBDDA1E</hash>
		<region>248</region>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<genreid>2048</genreid>
		<genre>Board game,Strategy,Action</genre>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<releasedate>19990207T230000</releasedate>
		<video>media/videos/Mario Party 617c831e01bfc270e875247a31334a69.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>media/thumbnails/Mario Party 45576e57fdcd874b4d0806b7e36c4fcc.png</thumbnail>
		<image>media/images/Mario Party aed85fea4a06503ca697187f31aa2c1f.png</image>
		<desc>You know Mario can jump. You know he can kick Bowser's tail from here to the moon, but we bet you didn't realize that Mario is the biggest party animal on the face of the Earth. Nintendo is throwing the most insane bash to ever hit the N64, and you're invited. For the first time, you'll catch a glimpse of how Mario celebrates all of the victories he's had over the years. 

Mario Party is unlike any other game for the N64, and it just might be the best party game to ever hit the system. Mario Party is designed for 1 to 4 players, but it's not really a party unless you're playing with your pals. The festivities are based on a board game format, right down to the fact that players must roll a die to determine how many spaces to move. The fun starts when players land on different squares, because each space holds one of more than fifty different mini-games. These quick competitions determine who will earn coins and stars, and who will go home empty handed. 

 The mini-games are spread over eight different game boards, all of which are not immediately available. Some of the games pit every man or princess against the others, some are two-on-two, and others are even three against one. The games are simple, but remarkably fun to play. One challenge is loosely based on "Simon Says," another involves a two-on-two bobsled race, and one crazy game makes one player attempt to cross a rope while the other three do their best to shake the player off. You'll find skill games, racing games, puzzle games --basically any type of challenge you could imagine. 

A good portion of the actual game boards are animated, with hidden dangers and special challenges scattered everywhere. Mario, Luigi, Princess Peach, Donkey Kong, Bowser, Yoshi, and Wario are all invited to the party, and each character has his or her own game board. 

Mario Party is fun for only one player, but to get the most out of this party-in-a-pak, you should play with three other friends. It's definitely the kind of game that will keep you up till the wee hours of the morning, so you might want to start catching up on your sleep right away.</desc>
		<rating>0.75000</rating>
		<name>Mario Party</name>
	</game>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1672717459">
		<path>Mario Party 2 (USA)/Mario Party 2 (USA).n64</path>
		<hash>9463D57A</hash>
		<region>248</region>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<genreid>2048</genreid>
		<genre>Board game,Action</genre>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<releasedate>20000123T230000</releasedate>
		<video>media/videos/Mario Party 2 856067f6bc03333887eb18485431ffb6.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>media/thumbnails/Mario Party 2 5aee5b75936550bbaff36ed0f1cdbe05.png</thumbnail>
		<image>media/images/Mario Party 2 9bcf9b9b08d6581b232562035e52fb3d.png</image>
		<desc>Mario and a range of well known Nintendo characters, including Yoshi, Bowser, Luigi, and Wario return for some more party action. 

The second edition includes 5 new boards, each with a specific theme, such as Space Land, Western Land, Horror Land, and Mystery Land. Each board includes unique attributes in relation to the theme, but the main goal is the same: complete the board game over a certain amount of moves and be the player to have the most coins and/or stars at the end. 

The single player story mode allows one person and 3 CPU controlled players to play each board. Once you play a specific mini-game (64 in all), they become available to purchase using the coins you collected in your games to play anytime. Multiplayer allows 2 to 4 people to play the game.</desc>
		<rating>0.80000</rating>
		<name>Mario Party 2</name>
	</game>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1672717459">
		<path>Mario Party 3 (USA)/Mario Party 3 (USA).n64</path>
		<hash>7A0987DD</hash>
		<region>248</region>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<genreid>2048</genreid>
		<genre>Board game,Action,Casual Game</genre>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<releasedate>20010506T230000</releasedate>
		<video>media/videos/Mario Party 3 eaa615b3a44d8cd41e7ad2a66c2b014d.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>media/thumbnails/Mario Party 3 be9abb35451c62dfd6fbd04c69bb3050.png</thumbnail>
		<image>media/images/Mario Party 3 3fc7bd484a069b190408eaeca0d5bc0d.png</image>
		<desc>The series continues with a set of 70 new mini-games.  Play in the new single-player Story mode, or bring in some friends for Party mode.  Four player games and a new two player mode are also available for play.

In Battle Royale mode (four player), you race around different boards to earn the most stars and coins.  At the end of each round, you face it off in one of the mini-games, which can be chicken chases, snowball fights, or various other competitions.

Duel mode allows play between just two people.  You still race around the board, but mini-games are only played when you land on a specific square.  Another play change is the addition of another character for your team, allowing tag team-style action in the game.

Story mode is essentially the same as a Battle Royale, except your opponents are played by the computer.</desc>
		<rating>0.75000</rating>
		<name>Mario Party 3</name>
	</game>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1672717459">
		<path>Paper Mario (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es) (1)/Paper Mario (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).n64</path>
		<hash>8C1804C9</hash>
		<region>83</region>
		<genreid>768</genreid>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<releasedate>20011004T230000</releasedate>
		<video>media/videos/Paper Mario 94ce2f6af382e85461d7bb3d09223a9d.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>media/thumbnails/Paper Mario a6b6422578dd0002f81cd8852044a3bc.png</thumbnail>
		<image>media/images/Paper Mario b4cbb8d16db5f8d5121e7fcddf8d1f67.png</image>
		<desc>Mario pals around in an all-new action adventure! Mario's back in his first adventure since Super Mario 64, and this time, Bowser's bent on preventing a storybook ending. When Princess Peach is kidnapped, Mario plots to rescue the seven Star Spirits and rid the Mushroom Kingdom of Koopa's cruel cohorts. As he travels from the tropical jungles of Lavalava Island to the frosty heights of Shiver Mountain, he'll meet up with seven all-new companions... and he'll need help from each one or there'll be no happily ever after.</desc>
		<rating>0.80000</rating>
		<name>Paper Mario</name>
	</game>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1672717467">
		<path>Super Mario 64 (USA)/Super Mario 64 (USA).n64</path>
		<hash>42C43204</hash>
		<region>248</region>
		<genreid>257</genreid>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<releasedate>19960925T230000</releasedate>
		<video>media/videos/Super Mario 64 af85c6794cd68f7f8855831df38da334.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>media/thumbnails/Super Mario 64 a769fc56aea83dec07c8964d0f476767.png</thumbnail>
		<image>media/images/Super Mario 64 8afe94069ac0ab51f29d269cf58905b6.png</image>
		<desc>Mario is super in a whole new way! Combining the finest 3-D graphics ever developed for a video game and an explosive sound track, Super Mario 64 becomes a new standard for video games. It's packed with bruising battles, daunting obstacle courses and underwater adventures. Retrieve the Power Stars from their hidden locations and confront your arch nemesis - Bowser, King of the Koopas!</desc>
		<rating>0.80000</rating>
		<name>Super Mario 64</name>
	</game>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1672717455">
		<path>Super Smash Bros. (USA)/Super Smash Bros. (USA).n64</path>
		<hash>DD2DF6D9</hash>
		<lastplayed>20220802T020553</lastplayed>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<region>248</region>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<genreid>262</genreid>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<releasedate>19990425T230000</releasedate>
		<video>media/videos/Super Smash Bros. 05f5fc89cf4eb9e7a0c48bbecc2d520d.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>media/thumbnails/Super Smash Bros. f01fa348595031d87b9b523b372b0ed8.png</thumbnail>
		<image>media/images/Super Smash Bros. 0ce297b99db950790e89c1de076264d0.png</image>
		<desc>Super Smash Brothers takes familiar Nintendo characters such as Mario, Kirby and Donkey Kong, and puts them into battle! There are 8 fully-interactive landscapes, with one for each character and noticeable links to their games. Controls are analogue-based, with different moves executed depending on the direction and how firmly the stick is pressed. Items like baseball bats, Bob-ombs, and healing items drop into the arenas at random, aiding any nearby characters than can make use of them. The game uses a fixed viewpoint which scrolls, although characters are rendered in 3D.

The one-player mode has 14 stages to work through. Up to 4 human players can do battle at once, with team play as well as all-against-all action. Hidden characters are thrown in for good measure, as are bonus rounds, and a battle to the end with a giant hand (yeah, you read right!).

Playable characters include: Captain Falcon* (F-Zero), Donkey Kong, Fox (Star Fox), Kirby, Jigglypuff* (Pokémon), Link (Legend of Zelda), Luigi* (Mario), Mario, Ness* (Mother/EarthBound), Pikachu (Pokémon), Samus (Metroid) and Yoshi (Mario)

*character must be unlocked first</desc>
		<rating>0.80000</rating>
		<name>Super Smash Bros.</name>
	</game>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1672717455">
		<path>Superman (U) (M3) [!]/Superman (U) (M3) [!].z64</path>
		<hash>437E3677</hash>
		<lastplayed>20220802T020740</lastplayed>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<region>248</region>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<genreid>256</genreid>
		<genre>Action,Action / Adventure</genre>
		<publisher>Titus</publisher>
		<developer>Titus</developer>
		<releasedate>19990530T230000</releasedate>
		<video>media/videos/Superman 8673fa9c3204a8bdfad340c84eb97560.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>media/thumbnails/Superman 20960d1956f2872f29180fceffb5f9b9.png</thumbnail>
		<image>media/images/Superman 965d6128ce221cd5dd46ce3a972ba02a.png</image>
		<desc>Lois Lane and Jimmy Olsen have disappeared - they've been kidnapped by the malevolent powers of Lex Luthor and Braniac, who have brought them into a virtual reality version of Metropolis. Superman must come to the rescue! The Man of Steel must work through this virtual dimension and find a way to conquer the evil masterminds that created it. Experience the incredible powers of Superman first-hand as you battle to rescue Lois Lane from the clutches of Metallo, then attempt to free Jimmy Olsen from the steel grip of Darkseid. Race into outer space to face Braniac's evil alien technology. Above all else, destroy Luthor's deadly dream of a virtual reality Metropolis!</desc>
		<rating>0.15000</rating>
		<name>Superman : The New Superman Adventures</name>
	</game>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1672717459">
		<path>Star Wars - Rogue Squadron (USA)/Star Wars - Rogue Squadron (USA).n64</path>
		<hash>2D6FA165</hash>
		<region>248</region>
		<genreid>256</genreid>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<developer>Factor 5</developer>
		<releasedate>19981116T230000</releasedate>
		<image>media/images/Star Wars - Rogue Squadron ae8382732fd173b31bf5bdfda2a9ecf3.png</image>
		<desc>Fly against the evil Empire! As Luke Skywalker, co-founder of the Rebel Alliance's elite Rogue Squadron, you must combat the evil Galactic Empire! Engage in intense, fast-paced planetary air-to-ground and air-to-air missions - dogfights, search and destroy, reconnaissance, bombing runs, rescue assignments and more! Pilot X-wings, Y-wings, A-wings, V-wings and Snowspeeders with powerful weapons in over 15 missions battling TIE fighters, TIE bombers, Imperial shuttles, AT-AT walkers, AT-STs and other challenging foes.</desc>
		<rating>0.90000</rating>
		<name>Star Wars : Rogue Squadron</name>
	</game>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1672717500">
		<path>LEGO Harry Potter - Years 1-4 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>LEGO Harry Potter - Years 1-4 (USA)</name>
	</game>
</gameList>
