<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1659465680">
		<path>1490 - Sonic Advance 3 (U)(Venom).zip</path>
		<hash>49DDA5E6</hash>
		<lastplayed>20220801T183829</lastplayed>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<region>248</region>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<genreid>257</genreid>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<releasedate>20040606T230000</releasedate>
		<video>media/videos/Sonic Advance 3 0ecb37b41fca6bb3f300901f736ab837.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>media/thumbnails/Sonic Advance 3 78e9e8954cafabb6af08201fea323fec.png</thumbnail>
		<image>media/images/Sonic Advance 3 362fe0608c47c5bf09d7580944c45d1d.png</image>
		<desc>Eggman has broken the world into seven parts, now the player must find the seven Chaos Emeralds to restore the world. 

Sonic Advance 3 is a Sonic game with a twist: the player can play with a friend in co-op mode or one of many multi-player modes like ring race. The game contains features from Sonic Advance and Sonic Advance 2, but with more options like choosing from 2 characters in story mode (a leading and a following character).</desc>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<rating>0.80000</rating>
		<name>Sonic Advance 3</name>
	</game>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1659465668">
		<path>Donkey Kong Country GBA.zip</path>
		<hash>41D277FE</hash>
		<lastplayed>20220801T175558</lastplayed>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<region>83</region>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<genreid>257</genreid>
		<genre>Platform,Action</genre>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<releasedate>20030608T230000</releasedate>
		<video>media/videos/Donkey Kong Country 58c7947f502639b5e299c7c1a46ec1a9.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>media/thumbnails/Donkey Kong Country fd3cada1bb615abcffd63604783a83bd.png</thumbnail>
		<image>media/images/Donkey Kong Country e3333ee371c2bf85d7582a1bea9e51ba.png</image>
		<desc>In Donkey Kong Country for Gameboy Advance, you play as Nintendo's famous gorilla. King K. Rool has stolen Donkey's bananas and he decides to go looking for them. Two characters are playable, Donkey is bigger and stronger, while Diddy is faster. It is possible to play in pairs, either in turns or in teams. Animals will help you get through certain levels and defeat the Kremlings.</desc>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<rating>0.64999</rating>
		<name>Donkey Kong Country</name>
	</game>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1659465852">
		<path>LEGO Star Wars - The Video Game (UE) (M7).zip</path>
		<hash>AEABFA5F</hash>
		<region>248</region>
		<genreid>256</genreid>
		<genre>Action,Action / Adventure</genre>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<developer>Griptonite Games</developer>
		<releasedate>20050328T230000</releasedate>
		<video>media/videos/Lego Star Wars - The Video Game ceeb77cb0348e7a7a3b21c4ab94f649b.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>media/thumbnails/Lego Star Wars - The Video Game 31aa644eb284a3b44c5c03791f5af560.png</thumbnail>
		<image>media/images/Lego Star Wars - The Video Game 17a8e91b63bcae28cd5455f1bfcf48ca.png</image>
		<desc>Lego Star Wars: The Video Game on GBA invites you to relive the trilogy of episodes I to III in the presence of the little yellow guys who can be dismantled. Rediscover the highlights of the movies and fight the Sith threat as many characters : powerful Jedi (including Obi-Wan Kenobi, Anakin Skywalker and Master Yoda), brave droids like R2-D2 or the clumsy Binks, Chewbacca the Wookie and many others.</desc>
		<rating>0.50000</rating>
		<name>LEGO Star Wars : The Video Game</name>
	</game>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1659465768">
		<path>Pac-Man Collection (U) [!].zip</path>
		<hash>6E5C16F4</hash>
		<region>248</region>
		<genreid>258</genreid>
		<genre>Action,Action / Labyrinth,Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<developer>Mass Media</developer>
		<releasedate>20010711T230000</releasedate>
		<video>media/videos/Pac-Man Collection 545d72c902901884e3c228c8b977b16d.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>media/thumbnails/Pac-Man Collection e8fd7241ed8d406d6417fd6cebae70dd.png</thumbnail>
		<image>media/images/Pac-Man Collection 10fe9a806feb39fa629c23755c48d260.png</image>
		<desc>Four classic Pac-Man games are included in this collection from Namco:

1. Pac-Man: The original arcade classic, complete and un-cut. 
2. Pac-Mania: A conversion of the 1987 update to Pac-Man, which takes the elements of the original arcade game and puts it into an isometric view, as well as adding the ability to jump.
3. Pac-Man Arrangement: Never re-produced outside of the arcade, Arrangement again uses the elements of the original Pac-Man and adds a fifth ghost, who can change shape and size when combined with the other 4 ghosts, and make life harder for Pac-Man. New power-ups are also included, like the ability to dash quickly around the screen, warp points to get from one place to the other and new ways of catching ghosts.
Pac-Attack: Like Tetris before it, you must fit falling blocks together to complete a line to clear the screen. In this case, the falling tiles also have ghosts in them, and once the Pac-Man tile appears (a tile with the Pac-Man symbol), Pac-Man will eat all of the ghosts that are in his path until he gets to a dead end.</desc>
		<rating>0.75000</rating>
		<name>Pac-Man Collection</name>
	</game>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1659465460">
		<path>Sims 2, The (UE) (M6).zip</path>
		<hash>8B1BC7DF</hash>
		<lastplayed>20220802T005447</lastplayed>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<region>248</region>
		<genreid>1024</genreid>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<developer>Amaze Entertainment</developer>
		<releasedate>20051023T230000</releasedate>
		<video>media/videos/Sims 2 The d0a0c09cde7e1573ff21b4dae4199dae.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>media/thumbnails/Sims 2 The 185fc4f975546d329a5ba34da658e4cb.png</thumbnail>
		<image>media/images/Sims 2 The 70d448947a95b5c12c69ff524df2e76b.png</image>
		<desc>Sims become stars in this platform-specific port of the popular PC sequel. From an isometric perspective similar to that of the original home computer version of The Sims, Game Boy Advance players guide their custom Sims 2 characters to tend to basic needs, interact with in-game objects, and make friends (or enemies) with other characters. Set in the extraterrestrial-friendly Strangetown, the game casts the player's character as the star of a hit "reality" television series, and the game's storyline progresses from one episode to the next, according to how well the character can stick to the script.</desc>
		<rating>0.70000</rating>
		<name>The Sims 2</name>
	</game>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1659465531">
		<path>Mario Party Advance (U).zip</path>
		<hash>F094A4CB</hash>
		<region>248</region>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<genreid>2048</genreid>
		<genre>Board game,Various</genre>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<developer>A.I</developer>
		<releasedate>20050327T230000</releasedate>
		<video>media/videos/Mario Party Advance 5fee91422d6aaa31aab06df92ee18c9b.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>media/thumbnails/Mario Party Advance ed4699299e3f57c7a7d7454f73256e20.png</thumbnail>
		<image>media/images/Mario Party Advance fddeabaa5b7d348ee5e2b3d6255fb4cb.png</image>
		<desc>The first portable incarnation of the Mario Party series, Mario Party Advance shakes things up quite a bit on the GBA.  With the focus on the single-player, there are all kinds of single-player mini-games, one giant single-player board to traverse instead of multiple ones (Shroom City), and all kinds of different Gaddgets and gameplay modes to indulge in.

The main single-player experience involves traveling across "Shroom City," which is a major departure from the standard set-up in past Mario Party titles.  You have the choice to be Mario, Luigi, Peach, or Yoshi, and depending on who you choose, you'll start at a different spot on the board, which is quite large.

You're given die rolls to navigate the board and, when you reach special sections of the map, complete special quests, which often involve helping residents of Shroom City and/or participating in special challenges.  Most quests involve collecting some sort of object elsewhere or a mini-game.  By completing these quests, you'll collect stars, which eventually allow for special boss bouts with Bowser, and you'll unlock mini-games and Gaddgets, which are simple, toy-like contraptions that you can play with.

The game ends when you complete your allotted number of turns, although additional turns and die rolls can be earned during the game by completing the "Mushroom Challenges" that occur rather often.  After completing your session, your rewards are saved, and you can play with your mini-games and Gaddgets in Play Mode.

There are also two additional modes available, "Party Land," where you can play special duel mini-games with a friend, and "Challenge Land," where you play through special modes that test your mini-game skills to earn coins, which can be used to purchase additional unlockables in a shop.

Finally, there is also a feature called the "Bonus Board."  You can play with a board that is included with the game using the GBA.  The GBA takes care of die rolls, mini-games, and end-of-the-game events.</desc>
		<rating>0.70000</rating>
		<name>Mario Party Advance</name>
	</game>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1659465748">
		<path>1277 - Mario And Luigi Superstar Saga (U)(Rising Sun).zip</path>
		<hash>E718D850</hash>
		<lastplayed>20220801T235440</lastplayed>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<region>248</region>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<genreid>768</genreid>
		<genre>Role playing games,Sports</genre>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<developer>Alpha Dream</developer>
		<releasedate>20031116T230000</releasedate>
		<video>media/videos/Mario And Luigi - Superstar Saga 23875224999bb984958193ee2af3f43f.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>media/thumbnails/Mario And Luigi - Superstar Saga c476e797e56339d9fb0c40297fa5f81b.png</thumbnail>
		<image>media/images/Mario And Luigi - Superstar Saga 10eae3c16616bdcc7071bdac4a6462a7.png</image>
		<desc>An evil witch has replaced Princess Peach's fair speech with explosives! Mario and Luigi must once again come to her rescue, but this time they employ the help of Bowser, their sworn enemy. Mario and Luigi must learn new moves and combine powers to fight off enemies and move closer to the witch's castle. Guide this unlikely bunch through an abundance of minigames such as Border Jump and Mystery Carts. Combine the powers of Mario and Luigi to pull off special tag-team moves. Immerse yourself in this bright, cartoonish, and humorous world, complete with hit music featured in previous Mario games.</desc>
		<rating>0.90000</rating>
		<name>Mario &amp; Luigi : Superstar Saga</name>
	</game>
	<game source="Recalbox" timestamp="1659465692">
		<path>Spider-Man - The Movie (U) [!].zip</path>
		<hash>406265B8</hash>
		<region>248</region>
		<genreid>257</genreid>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<developer>Digital Eclipse</developer>
		<releasedate>20020415T230000</releasedate>
		<video>media/videos/Spider-man 7516c1f7424d35eca6756c1677d51b2e.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>media/thumbnails/Spider-man ba2a14d62bc2401c30e9b570fcc24272.png</thumbnail>
		<image>media/images/Spider-man 50c5f70325be0da9c45c793eec7eba07.png</image>
		<desc>Spider-Man, the classic comic book co-created by Stan Lee, is now a major motion picture. This conversion of the movie to the video game world takes the major storyline, characters and artwork of the Spider-Man movie and adds a lengthy backstory and new characters.

The Green Goblin is the main villian here, and as Peter Parker you must defy gravity using your spider crawl, web-slinging and spider-sense abilities to track down Spidey's nemesis through the skyscapers of New York City.

The major inclusion for this title over the previous Spider-Man series (on Playstation also by Activision) is aerial combat. Attack the enemy mid-air while web-slinging, rise and decend while swinging and banking around buildings create a greater emphasis on Spidey's greatest asset, the spider web.</desc>
		<rating>0.90000</rating>
		<name>Spider-Man</name>
	</game>
</gameList>
